Sonali Shinde

Digital Marketing & Social Media Executive

Phone Number: 7678047851 **Email Id:** shindesonali361@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Digital Marketing Executive with over 5 years of successful experience in Social Media management. Recognized consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success in the Digital Marketing industry. Strengths in Social Media Marketing and Social Campaign Management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov 2022 – August 2023 Marketing & Sales Lead Connate, Mumbai

- Create engaging, original content for different social media platforms, including written posts, images, and videos
- Manage day-to-day social media activities, including posting, responding to comments, and engaging with followers.
- Build and maintain a content calendar to ensure a consistent and cohesive online presence.
- Implement paid social media advertising campaigns to drive brand awareness and conversions.
- Monitor and analyze social media trends, audience insights, and performance metrics to refine strategies.
- Study client profiles and write an executive summary.
- Coordinate with the team to learn about the NetSuite Portal like creating PDR and E-mail Marketing.
- Coordinate with clients for sales-related activities etc.
- Qualifying the incoming leads, follow-up with leads for appointment
- Coordinate with OEM Oracle to learn latest marketing strategies

Jan 2022 – Sep 2022 Social Media Executive Asesa Soft, Pune

- Management of operational aspects of social media in all terms.
- Delivering presentations to clients for social media and digital marketing services.
- Alliance with Food & Fashion Blogger to help in their business start-ups and expansion.
- Preparing monthly reports for social media & and food ordering apps for respective clients
- Regular coordination with the client regarding requirements & and management of the client's social mediaplatforms.
- Content creation for social media platforms for Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, etc.
- Strategic planning for business promotion and new perspective clients.

Nov 2019 – Jan 2022 Digital Marketing Executive Matrix Bricks, Navi Mumbai

- Coordinate with clients to develop social media pages to promote businesses.
- Produced and submitted weekly or monthly reports to clients regarding the campaigns
- Create content for social media posts & and posts on social handles.
- Create a campaign on Facebook & and LinkedIn like Lead Generation & Page Likes.
- Replying to comments & and queries on the post.
- On a weekly basis follow up with clients related to social handles.
- Create social media PPT including proposals and presentations for clients.
- Strategic planning for business promotion and new prospective clients.

Dec 2018 to June 2019 Social Media Executive Bluetan. Mumbai

- Management of operational aspects of social media in all terms.
- Delivering presentations to clients for social media and digital marketing services.
- Alliance with Food & Fashion Blogger to help in their business start-ups and expansion.
- Preparing monthly reports for social media and food and ordering apps for respective clients
- Regular coordination with the client regarding requirements & and management of the client's social mediaplatforms.
- Content creation for social media platforms for Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, etc.

March to July 2018 Digital Intern

Eyecatchers Digital Agency, Thane

- Execution of off-page SEO on search engine websites like Google.
- Performing client background research and SEO Audit trials for new clients
- Preparing monthly SME/SEO calendars for respective clients
- Preparation of monthly reports on time for clients, based on their Social Media engagements & activities.
- Engaged and execute Keyword Research analysis on Keyword planner.

EDUCATION DETAILS

Bachelor of Commerce - The year 2017

K B College of Arts, Commerce, and Science – Secured First Class

Higher Secondary Certification – The year 2014

K B College of Arts, Commerce, and Science – Secured First Class

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION

- ✓ Advanced Digital Marketing Diploma from DMTI SoftPro Training Division
- ✓ Google Certification AdWords Search Certification
- ✓ Google ads course from PIIDM Institute

SKILLS & KNOWLEDGE

- Social Media Management and Advertising
- On-Page & Off-Page SEO
- Google Analytical Skills
- Email Marketing
- Word Press

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address : Shivsrushti Apartment, Amrut CitY, Jambhulwadi Rd, Shani Nagar, 411046

Husband's Name : Mr. Shardul Ulhalkar

Marital Status : Married

Birthday : August 20, 1996

Gender : Female

Languages Known : English Hindi & Marathi

I, SONALI SHINDE hereby declare that the above information I true & correct to the best of my knowledge Place: Pune